{
 "subject": "chemistry",
 "lesson": "l01",
 "grade": "c8",
 "quests": [
			{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "The liquid metal used in thermometers is",
		"options": {
			"a": "copper",
			"b": "mercury",
			"c": "silver",
			"d": "gold"
	},
			"answer": "b"
		},
		{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "The pictorial symbol for water given bythe alchemists was",
		"options": {
			"a": "Solid angle",
			"b": "Accuracy",
			"c": "Temperature",
			"d": "Plane angle"
	},
			"answer": "b"
	},
		{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "Which one of the following element nameis not derived from planet?",
		"options": {
			"a": "Plutonium",
			"b": "Neptunium",
			"c": "Uranium",
			"d": "Mercury"
	},
			"answer": "d"
	},
		{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Symbol of mercury is",
		"options": {
			"a": "Ag",
			"b": "Hg",
			"c": "Au",
			"d": "Pb"
	},
			"answer": "b"
	},
		{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "A form of non-metal which has highductility is ",
		"options": {
			"a": "nitrogen",
			"b": "oxygen",
			"c": "chlorine",
			"d": "carbon"
	},
			"answer": "d"
	},
		{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "The property which allows the metals to be hammered into their sheets is___________",
		"options": {
			"a": "ductility",
			"b": "malleability",
			"c": "conductivity",
			"d": "kilogram"
	},
		"answer": "b"
	},
		{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "The non-metal which conducts electriccurrent is ",
		"options": {
			"a": "carbon",
			"b": "oxygen",
			"c": "aluminium",
			"d": "sulphu"
	},
		"answer": "a"
	},
		{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "Pencil lead contains ",
		"options": {
			"a": "graphite",
			"b": "diamond",
			"c": "aluminium",
			"d": "sulphur"
	},
		"answer": "a"
	},
		{
		"id": 9,
	"question": "Identify the state of matter based on the arrangement of the molecules. ",
	"options": {
			"a": "A - Gas, B - Solid, C - Liquid",
			"b": "A - Liquid, B - Solid, C - Gas",
			"c": "A - Gas, B - Solid, C - Liquid",
			"d": "A - Liquid, B - Gas, C - Solid"
	},
		"answer": "a"
	},
		{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "For making wires ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Iron",
			"b": "Copper",
			"c": "Tungsten",
			"d": "Boren"
	},
		"answer": "b"
	},
		{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Sewing needle ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Iron",
			"b": "Copper",
			"c": "tungsten",
			"d": "Boren"
	},
		"answer": "a"
	},
		{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "As a fuel for ignition in rocket ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Iron",
			"b": "Copper",
			"c": "tungsten",
			"d": "Boren"
	},
		"answer": "d"
	},
		{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Making the filament of a bulb ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Iron",
			"b": "Copper",
			"c": "Tungsten",
			"d": "Boren"
	},
		"answer": "c"
	},
		{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "Building block of matter ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Atom",
			"b": "Element",
			"c": "Compound ",
			"d": "Molecule "
	},
		"answer": "a"
	},
		{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "Atoms of different kinds ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Atom",
			"b": "Element",
			"c": "Compound ",
			"d": "Molecule "
	},
		"answer": "b"
	},
		{
		"id": 16,
		"question": "Atoms of the same kind ",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": " ",
			"d": " "
	},
		"answer": "b"
	},
		{
		"id": 17,
		"question": "Smallest unit of a substance ",
		"options": {
			"a": "Atom",
			"b": "Element",
			"c": "Compound ",
			"d": "Molecule "
	},
		"answer": "d"
	}
  ]
}